<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Sam&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://ssguyah.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Sam&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 18:13:24 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ssguyah.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Rejection Letter</title>
      <link>https://ssguyah.com/posts/rejection/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 16:12:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ssguyah.com/posts/rejection/</guid>
      <description>Currency Converter I currently received a rejection letter of my number one choice company after an over the phone interview. I felt pretty bummed about the entire situation so I decided to write out a complete solution for the technical question I was asked. You can check out the Github here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ares</title>
      <link>https://ssguyah.com/posts/ares/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 15:01:46 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ssguyah.com/posts/ares/</guid>
      <description>What is it that drives me perilously into that void?
Is it the end goal of setting foot on a red god? I’ve dreamt of it a thousand times. I’ve seen my feet, in boots made of unbreakable material, dig the first human footstep deep into the planets surface. There is line of red copper surrounding my feet. The red world and I would become one; as one trembles in awe of its first connection, so would the other; interconnected with the first breath we took.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>War?!</title>
      <link>https://ssguyah.com/posts/war/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 14:53:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ssguyah.com/posts/war/</guid>
      <description>I believe that it takes a certain amount of comfortability within yourself demanded by the solitude – or in many cases,loneliness – of academic study. It is not the difficulty per say, but the constant bombardment of new information that must digested and regurgitated at such a constant and seemingly never ending pace by yourself can be excruciating. The material is not hard, and maybe there in lies another problem of the academic venture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twisted</title>
      <link>https://ssguyah.com/posts/twisted/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 14:50:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ssguyah.com/posts/twisted/</guid>
      <description>The world is twisted.
It has bent out of proportion by the ruling few who can only see the world through their eyes.; an unphilosophical bunch that can neither see the world upside down nor right side up. They stand for very little and rob on thing. What little minuscule ideas they hold about mathematics, literature, film, anthropology, engineering, philosophy, paintings, biology, music, metaphysics, history, and economics, have very little bases on fact and evidence; if in fact they even speculate on the nature of the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Closer</title>
      <link>https://ssguyah.com/posts/closer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 14:45:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ssguyah.com/posts/closer/</guid>
      <description>I thought I knew a girl once. This was years ago. She was lovely when I first met her. Filled with joy and wonder and about things and life. We were young, high school friends that read too much and talked to loud about it. We were our own group of outcasts; ones that liked to enjoy listening to the echoing of dead men’s minds scratched down on print. To us, the voices were like sleigh bells bringing knowledge and forthcoming joy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bad Mornings</title>
      <link>https://ssguyah.com/posts/bad-mornings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 14:42:30 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ssguyah.com/posts/bad-mornings/</guid>
      <description>WRITTEN ON Thursday, January 8th 2017 10:48pm
A certain grimy existence lives on the dirt of olds cars and foggy morning skies. An impure and grotesque air lives in the morning that I now find to be the bane of my very existence, and will probably be the reason this semester is not the proud and upright semester I’d like it to be. In all honesty, because of the morning beams that begin to — but never fully — warm my body, to the depressing colors of a house in the rising sun, to all around sluggish sense of movement in ones body, mornings are the absolute fucking worst time of the day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brown_2</title>
      <link>https://ssguyah.com/posts/brown_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 14:27:09 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ssguyah.com/posts/brown_2/</guid>
      <description>Long are the days of township solitude. But solitude held little connotation to the norm definition. Solitude meant that nobody around you knew who you were. People of all creeds still interacted with you because the density of the city forced people to be open and socially capable of the many endeavors it took to know a stranger. With high respect and courtesy you would reciprocate the same social wellbeing onto the them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meh?</title>
      <link>https://ssguyah.com/posts/meh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 14:19:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ssguyah.com/posts/meh/</guid>
      <description>Is ignorance really bliss?
Can ignorance be really what this is?
How do define such abstractions
If they can’t be seen as actions?
I’m having a hard time changing.
Guess that’s the main thing.
A part of me wants to stay
And slowly fade away.
Use to call it a demon
Now I’m dreamin.
It was something I had to fight until I gave it all
Now I’m questioning if I should just hang real tall</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Student Body Blues</title>
      <link>https://ssguyah.com/posts/student-body-blues/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 14:07:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ssguyah.com/posts/student-body-blues/</guid>
      <description>Before I begin, please do not misinterpret me: I do not care for the life of every individual that comprises the Florida Atlantic Student body. To be very clear, when I look around me and see only dilapidated and demotivated faces, my first thought is not to help every single one I see, but to analyze why they feel the way they do and to avoid the cause of their suffering at all costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brown_1</title>
      <link>https://ssguyah.com/posts/brown_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 13:48:44 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ssguyah.com/posts/brown_1/</guid>
      <description>Dealing with pain. God damn I was never any good at it. Pain was the enemy for the longest. I despised its presence and reaped nothing from it when it was present. They say that there are two kinds of pain, one that makes you stronger, and one that it useless. My mind has been scattered to the fucking wind.
I woke up at 8:30pm today. This will be a long night; I have faced longer nights in the past though.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Walk With God</title>
      <link>https://ssguyah.com/posts/a-walk-with-god/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 13:34:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ssguyah.com/posts/a-walk-with-god/</guid>
      <description>And as god fell one piece a time, through the ashed gray, he called out to the child for help. And for all the suffering that was given to the child, after all the lost loves that was burdened through his ever growing days, the child reached out and saved god from his own tragedies. And god grabbed back with ever growing force, reluctant to ever look into his savior’s eyes again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Definition of Art</title>
      <link>https://ssguyah.com/posts/a-definition-of-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 23:54:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ssguyah.com/posts/a-definition-of-art/</guid>
      <description>Art is useless because its aim is simply to create a mood. It is not meant to instruct, or to influence action in any way. It is superbly sterile, and the note of its pleasure is sterility. If the contemplation of a work of art is followed by activity of any kind, the work is either of a very second-rate order, or the spectator has failed to realise the complete artistic impression.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To the End</title>
      <link>https://ssguyah.com/posts/to-the-end/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 17:12:53 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ssguyah.com/posts/to-the-end/</guid>
      <description>I held tightly to the belief that I would one day be a god. I awaited for it, praised its coming, even went so far as to dream for it. I realize now that it is a curse, and a great sadness arises from its coming.
I am glad that I am only human. I am glad that my days are numbered because it makes every day count more; it puts an energy into all that I do for I know that nothing is infinite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Girl (Haiku)</title>
      <link>https://ssguyah.com/posts/my-girl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 11:54:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ssguyah.com/posts/my-girl/</guid>
      <description>My girlfriend is cool
She makes me very happy
I love her a lot</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Murakami the Artist</title>
      <link>https://ssguyah.com/posts/murakami-the-artist/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 11:26:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ssguyah.com/posts/murakami-the-artist/</guid>
      <description>It is a if every time I read one of his works I begin to catch myself, periodically through out the day, dreaming of nondescript facades of truly empty people living lives that question the very meaning of what it is to be a human being. His literature is paintings of life I never once experienced before; it casts me into an ocean of fear and serenity that I wish to never escape from.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I Learned in Four Years</title>
      <link>https://ssguyah.com/posts/what-i-know/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 21:50:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ssguyah.com/posts/what-i-know/</guid>
      <description>As the new fall semester begins, so to does the yearly drudge and tiring exhalations of students and faculty heard through out the halls like background noise to a horror film. It is not pretty. The pursuit of pure knowledge, degrees,and ultimately a higher position in society were never designed to be an aesthetically pleasing journey.
But this is fall. I am about to begin the final year of a four year journey and in a few short months, receive a Bachelors Degree in Computer Science (hopefully with honors if nothing to dramatically terrible happens to my GPA) and begin my career in the tech field.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>