<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sam&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://ssguyah.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sam&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 17:12:53 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ssguyah.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>To the End</title>
      <link>https://ssguyah.com/posts/to-the-end/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 17:12:53 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ssguyah.com/posts/to-the-end/</guid>
      <description>I held tightly to the belief that I would one day be a god. I awaited for it, praised its coming, even went so far as to dream for it. I realize now that it is a curse, and a great sadness arises from its coming.
I am glad that I am only human. I am glad that my days are numbered because it makes every day count more; it puts an energy into all that I do for I know that nothing is infinite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Girl (Haiku)</title>
      <link>https://ssguyah.com/posts/my-girl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 11:54:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ssguyah.com/posts/my-girl/</guid>
      <description>My girlfriend is cool
She makes me very happy
I love her a lot</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Murakami the Artist</title>
      <link>https://ssguyah.com/posts/murakami-the-artist/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 11:26:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ssguyah.com/posts/murakami-the-artist/</guid>
      <description>It is a if every time I read one of his works I begin to catch myself, periodically through out the day, dreaming of nondescript facades of truly empty people living lives that question the very meaning of what it is to be a human being. His literature is paintings of life I never once experienced before; it casts me into an ocean of fear and serenity that I wish to never escape from.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I Learned in Four Years</title>
      <link>https://ssguyah.com/posts/what-i-know/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 21:50:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ssguyah.com/posts/what-i-know/</guid>
      <description>As the new fall semester begins, so to does the yearly drudge and tiring exhalations of students and faculty heard through out the halls like background noise to a horror film. It is not pretty. The pursuit of pure knowledge, degrees, and ultimately a higher position in society were never designed to be an aesthetically pleasing journey.
But this is fall. I am about to begin the final year of a four year journey and in a few short months, receive a Bachelors Degree in Computer Science (hopefully with honors if nothing to dramatically terrible happens to my GPA) and begin my career in the tech field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://ssguyah.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2018 20:52:39 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ssguyah.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello! I&amp;rsquo;m Samuel Septimus Guyah, current Senior at Florida Atlantic University studying Computer Science. This blog contains my thoughts on Computer Science, Mathematics, Literature, Philosophy, love, and generally any subject I find appealing to write about.
Most of my free time is spent with my girlfriend, at the gym, or on my machine learning side project.
You can reach me through my email.
Please enjoy!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>