<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Philosophy on Sam&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://ssguyah.com/tags/philosophy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Philosophy on Sam&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 23:54:03 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ssguyah.com/tags/philosophy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Definition of Art</title>
      <link>https://ssguyah.com/posts/a-definition-of-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 23:54:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ssguyah.com/posts/a-definition-of-art/</guid>
      <description>Art is useless because its aim is simply to create a mood. It is not meant to instruct, or to influence action in any way. It is superbly sterile, and the note of its pleasure is sterility. If the contemplation of a work of art is followed by activity of any kind, the work is either of a very second-rate order, or the spectator has failed to realise the complete artistic impression.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I Learned in Four Years</title>
      <link>https://ssguyah.com/posts/what-i-know/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 21:50:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ssguyah.com/posts/what-i-know/</guid>
      <description>As the new fall semester begins, so to does the yearly drudge and tiring exhalations of students and faculty heard through out the halls like background noise to a horror film. It is not pretty. The pursuit of pure knowledge, degrees, and ultimately a higher position in society were never designed to be an aesthetically pleasing journey.
But this is fall. I am about to begin the final year of a four year journey and in a few short months, receive a Bachelors Degree in Computer Science (hopefully with honors if nothing to dramatically terrible happens to my GPA) and begin my career in the tech field.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>